so let's look at the speed versus power
with his weight versus cost quiz answer
we were asked which one of these is the
worst laptop processor the crawley on
slow in lab team fast mhmm
and Birnam where performance is growing
but the battery life is decreasing the
weight is growing and the cost is
growing well most of these are actually
not very good processors lap tiem seems
reasonable it gives you good performance
five hour battery life is not too bad
four hours is for the processor you can
build a laptop with that and about $100
for the processor the laptop will
probably be about $1000 so that's fine
going with the slow iam it's not too bad
it's gonna be half as fast but you can
still do a lot of things with it it
gives you excellent battery life
possibly even lighter laptop and it's
going to be cheap so these two are
probably reasonable up to processors
faciem is a lot faster very little
battery life you'll probably have to
keep it plugged in it's relatively heavy
so this is gonna be a very heavy laptop
and it's gonna be more expensive but
it's still not an unreasonable laptop so
clearly the designs in the middle are
actually better laptop processors than
the ones on the extremes so what we
really have to do is decide whether the
chromium or the bernam is the worst
laptop processor here we have something
that is about 1/10 of a performance of a
reasonable laptop processor extremely
good battery life probably you could
make this as big as a cell phone and
very very cheap so this is not such a
bad processor there are still things you
can do with it and some people might
want a laptop this of this kind in
contrast here we have something that has
four times the performance of the lab
team the battery life of all of 2
minutes 20 pounds for the processor
including the heatsink and so on so
probably this is not really gonna be
portable and it's gonna be extremely
extremely expensive so as you can see
the highest performance processor here
is actually the worst laptop processor
so as you can see between the chromium
and the bernam here we have something
that is very slow but also very light
and has a long battery life which is
probably
better than having something that is
significantly faster with almost no
battery life spinal injuries from
carrying it around and extremely
expensive so when you drop it you drop
$15,000 worth of laptop and you will
drop it